(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,t,i){},15:function(e,t,i){"use strict";i.r(t);var n=i(1),s=i.n(n),r=i(8),a=i.n(r),o=(i(13),i(2)),d=[{name:"Nintendo quiz",id:1,questions:[{rightAnswerId:2,question:"Who is the face of nintedo?",id:1,answers:[{text:"Sonic",id:1},{text:"Mario",id:2},{text:"Kirby",id:3},{text:"Link",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:1,question:"Which nintendo game involes fighting and nintendo characters?",id:2,answers:[{text:"Super Smash Bros",id:1},{text:"Dave guy",id:2},{text:"Cars 2",id:3},{text:"sonic free riders",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:1,question:"Who is Nintendos main rival?",id:3,answers:[{text:"Sega",id:1},{text:"Microsoft",id:2},{text:"Sony",id:3},{text:"The founder",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:4,question:"What was the name of Nintendo's least successful home console?",id:4,answers:[{text:"The Game Boy",id:1},{text:"The Megadrive",id:2},{text:"The WII U",id:3},{text:"The Virtual Boy",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:4,question:"Which of the following is NOT a kirby game?",id:5,answers:[{text:"Kirby Tilt'n Tumble",id:1},{text:"Kirby and The Fighters",id:2},{text:"Kirby Air Ride",id:3},{text:"Kirby Battle!",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:4,question:"How long had Nintendo wanted Yoshi to be in the Mario series?",id:6,answers:[{text:"Since Donkey Kong",id:1},{text:"Since Mario 3",id:2},{text:"Since early development of Super Mario World",id:3},{text:"Since Super Mario Brothers",id:4}]}]},{name:"Video Games Trivia",id:2,questions:[{rightAnswerId:2,question:" What was the name of the videogame designer who created the Mario, The Legend of Zelda, and Star Fox franchises?",id:1,answers:[{text:"Mario Linguini",id:1},{text:"Shigeru Miyamoto",id:2},{text:"Fusajiro Yamauchi",id:3},{text:"Ken Kutaragi",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:2,question:"What is the setting/era of the original Call of Duty?",id:2,answers:[{text:"WW1",id:1},{text:"WW2",id:2},{text:"WW3",id:3},{text:"The Cold War",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:1,question:"What classic video game did Tony Stark catch a member of S.H.I.E.L.D. playing in the first Avengers movie?",id:3,answers:[{text:"Galaga",id:1},{text:"Pac-Man",id:2},{text:"Mortal Kombat",id:3},{text:"Frogger",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:3,question:"Which video game holds the record for having the highest budget to ever produce?",id:4,answers:[{text:"Halo 5: Guardians",id:1},{text:"Call of Duty: Black Ops III",id:2},{text:"Grand Theft Auto V",id:3},{text:"Guitar Hero",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:2,question:"What are the professions of Mario and Luigi?",id:5,answers:[{text:"Chefs",id:1},{text:"Plumbers",id:2},{text:"Doctors",id:3},{text:"Race-car drivers",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:3,question:"A computer opponent's ability to adaptively challenge a player is known as what?",id:6,answers:[{text:"Asymmetric gameplay",id:1},{text:"Asynchronous gameplay",id:2},{text:"Artificial Intelligence",id:3},{text:"Attract mode",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:2,question:"Pok\xe9mon was originally released on which video game console?",id:7,answers:[{text:"Nintendo 64",id:1},{text:"Gameboy",id:2},{text:"Gameboy Advanced",id:3},{text:"Gameboy SD",id:4}]}]},{name:"Healthy snacks",id:3,questions:[{rightAnswerId:4,question:"According to Canada's Food guide every snack should have what?",id:1,answers:[{text:"Sugar",id:1},{text:"Milk",id:2},{text:"Protein",id:3},{text:"Fruit and/or Vegetable",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:2,question:"Which is NOT a whole grain?",id:2,answers:[{text:"popcorn",id:1},{text:"white rice",id:2},{text:"oats",id:3},{text:"quinoa",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:1,question:"With apple slices and a nut (almond, peanut, sunflower) butter. The nut butter is a what?",id:3,answers:[{text:"protein",id:1},{text:"fruit",id:2},{text:"vegetable",id:3},{text:"sugar",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:1,question:"Preparing snacks ahead of time helps you choose healthier options",id:4,answers:[{text:"true",id:1},{text:"false",id:2}]},{rightAnswerId:4,question:"What are (is an) easy way(s) to have snacks prepared?",id:5,answers:[{text:"Chop extra vegetables when cooking so you'll have some for snacks",id:1},{text:"Hard-cook eggs on the weekend. They will keep for a week in the fridge with the shell on",id:2},{text:"Make your own train mix. Toss together whole grain cereal, nuts seeds and dried fruits",id:3},{text:"All of the above",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:2,question:"Choose the HEALTHIEST snack option",id:6,answers:[{text:"whole grain goldfish crackers",id:1},{text:"cucumber and peppers with hummus",id:2},{text:"potato chips",id:3},{text:"cheese wiz on white bread",id:4}]},{rightAnswerId:3,question:" Choose the HEALTHIEST snack option",id:7,answers:[{text:"glass of fruit juice",id:1},{text:"tortilla chips and salsa",id:2},{text:"popcorn and guacamole",id:3},{text:"fruit to go",id:4}]}]}],c=i(6),h=i(0),u=function(e){var t=e.question,i=e.answers,n=e.onClick,s=e.rightAnswerId,r=e.shouldShowCorrect;return Object(h.jsxs)(h.Fragment,{children:[Object(h.jsx)("h2",{className:"test-header",children:t}),Object(h.jsx)("ul",{className:"button-container",children:i.map((function(e){return Object(h.jsx)("li",{style:{backgroundColor:s===e.id&&r?"green":"none"},onClick:function(){return n(e.id)},className:"answer",children:e.text},e.id)}))})]})},l=s.a.createContext(),x=function(e){var t=e.userAnswers,i=t.filter((function(e){return!0===e}));console.log(i);var s=Object(n.useContext)(l).returnToHome;return Object(h.jsxs)(h.Fragment,{children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"quiz-finish",children:[i.length/t.length*100>=80?"Wow, you are a genius!":i.length/t.length*100>=50?"Not bad!":"I am sure you could do better!"," "]}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"quiz-finish-counter",children:"You gave ".concat(i.length," right answers out of ").concat(t.length," questions")}),Object(h.jsx)("h2",{className:"quiz-return-home",onClick:function(){return s()},children:"Return to home"})]})},g=function(e){var t=e.listOfQuize,i=Object(n.useState)(0),s=Object(o.a)(i,2),r=s[0],a=s[1],d=Object(n.useState)([]),l=Object(o.a)(d,2),g=l[0],w=l[1],m=function(e){g.length-1!==r&&(t[r].rightAnswerId===e?w([].concat(Object(c.a)(g),[!0])):w([].concat(Object(c.a)(g),[!1])),setTimeout((function(){a(r+1)}),2e3))},b=null===t||void 0===t?void 0:t.map((function(e){return Object(h.jsx)(h.Fragment,{children:Object(h.jsx)(u,{shouldShowCorrect:g.length-1===r,onClick:m,question:e.question,answers:e.answers,rightAnswerId:e.rightAnswerId},e.id)})}));return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"test-container",children:[r<=(null===t||void 0===t?void 0:t.length)-1?b[r]:Object(h.jsx)(x,{userAnswers:g}),r!==(null===t||void 0===t?void 0:t.length)&&Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"counter",children:"".concat(r+1,"/").concat(null===t||void 0===t?void 0:t.length)})]})},w=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)(d),t=Object(o.a)(e,2),i=t[0],s=(t[1],Object(n.useState)(0)),r=Object(o.a)(s,2),a=r[0],c=r[1];return Object(h.jsx)(l.Provider,{value:{returnToHome:function(){c(0)}},children:Object(h.jsxs)(h.Fragment,{children:[Object(h.jsx)("h2",{className:"quiz-header",children:"Take a look at our amazing quizes!"}),0===a?Object(h.jsx)("ul",{className:"quiz-list",children:i.map((function(e){return Object(h.jsx)("li",{className:"quiz-list-item",onClick:function(){return t=e.id,void c(t);var t},children:e.name},e.id)}))}):Object(h.jsx)(g,{listOfQuize:i[a-1].questions})]})})};a.a.render(Object(h.jsx)(s.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"app-body",children:Object(h.jsx)(w,{})})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[15,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.f51271a3.chunk.js.map